<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Movie Catalogue</string>
  <string name="movies">Movies</string>
  <string name="tv_show">TV Show</string>

  <!--Detail Activity Values-->
  <string name="overview">Overview</string>
  <string name="dummy_title">Dragon Ball Super: Broly</string>
  <string name="dummy_synopsis">Earth is peaceful following the Tournament of Power. Realizing that the universes still hold many more strong people yet to see, Goku spends all his days training to reach even greater heights. Then one day, Goku and Vegeta are faced by a Saiyan called \'Broly\' who they\'ve never seen before. The Saiyans were supposed to have been almost completely wiped out in the destruction of Planet Vegeta, so what\'s this one doing on Earth? This encounter between the three Saiyans who have followed completely different destinies turns into a stupendous battle, with even Frieza (back from Hell) getting caught up in the mix.</string>

  <string-array name="data_title">
    <item>A Star Is Born</item>
    <item>Aquaman</item>
    <item>Avengers: Infinity War</item>
    <item>Bird Box</item>
    <item>Bohemian Rhapsody</item>
    <item>Bumblebee</item>
    <item>Creed</item>
    <item>Deadpool</item>
    <item>Dragon Ball Super: Broly</item>
    <item>How to Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</item>
  </string-array>
  <string-array name="data_synopsis">
    <item>Seasoned musician Jackson Maine discovers - and falls in love with - struggling artist Ally. She has just about given up on her dream to make it big as a singer - until Jack coaxes her into the spotlight. But even as Ally\'s career takes off, the personal side of their relationship is breaking down, as Jack fights an ongoing battle with his own internal demons.</item>
    <item>Once home to the most advanced civilization on Earth, Atlantis is now an underwater kingdom ruled by the power-hungry King Orm. With a vast army at his disposal, Orm plans to conquer the remaining oceanic people and then the surface world. Standing in his way is Arthur Curry, Orm\'s half-human, half-Atlantean brother and true heir to the throne.</item>
    <item>As the Avengers and their allies have continued to protect the world from threats too large for any one hero to handle, a new danger has emerged from the cosmic shadows: Thanos. A despot of intergalactic infamy, his goal is to collect all six Infinity Stones, artifacts of unimaginable power, and use them to inflict his twisted will on all of reality. Everything the Avengers have fought for has led up to this moment - the fate of Earth and existence itself has never been more uncertain.</item>
    <item>Five years after an ominous unseen presence drives most of society to suicide, a survivor and her two children make a desperate bid to reach safety.</item>
    <item>Singer Freddie Mercury, guitarist Brian May, drummer Roger Taylor and bass guitarist John Deacon take the music world by storm when they form the rock \'n\' roll band Queen in 1970. Hit songs become instant classics. When Mercury\'s increasingly wild lifestyle starts to spiral out of control, Queen soon faces its greatest challenge yet – finding a way to keep the band together amid the success and excess.</item>
    <item>On the run in the year 1987, Bumblebee finds refuge in a junkyard in a small Californian beach town. Charlie, on the cusp of turning 18 and trying to find her place in the world, discovers Bumblebee, battle-scarred and broken. When Charlie revives him, she quickly learns this is no ordinary yellow VW bug.</item>
    <item>The former World Heavyweight Champion Rocky Balboa serves as a trainer and mentor to Adonis Johnson, the son of his late friend and former rival Apollo Creed.</item>
    <item>Deadpool tells the origin story of former Special Forces operative turned mercenary Wade Wilson, who after being subjected to a rogue experiment that leaves him with accelerated healing powers, adopts the alter ego Deadpool. Armed with his new abilities and a dark, twisted sense of humor, Deadpool hunts down the man who nearly destroyed his life.</item>
    <item>Earth is peaceful following the Tournament of Power. Realizing that the universes still hold many more strong people yet to see, Goku spends all his days training to reach even greater heights. Then one day, Goku and Vegeta are faced by a Saiyan called \'Broly\' who they\'ve never seen before. The Saiyans were supposed to have been almost completely wiped out in the destruction of Planet Vegeta, so what\'s this one doing on Earth? This encounter between the three Saiyans who have followed completely different destinies turns into a stupendous battle, with even Frieza (back from Hell) getting caught up in the mix.</item>
    <item>As Hiccup fulfills his dream of creating a peaceful dragon utopia, Toothless\' discovery of an untamed, elusive mate draws the Night Fury away. When danger mounts at home and Hiccup’s reign as village chief is tested, both dragon and rider must make impossible decisions to save their kind.</item>
  </string-array>
  <array name="data_photo">
    <item>@drawable/poster_a_star</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_aquaman</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_avengerinfinity</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_birdbox</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_bohemian</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_bumblebee</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_creed</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_deadpool</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_dragonball</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_dragon</item>
  </array>

  <string-array name="tv_show_title">
    <item>All I Want for Love is You</item>
    <item>Captain Tsubasa</item>
    <item>Insatiable</item>
    <item>Krypton</item>
    <item>Legacies</item>
    <item>Rascal Does Not Dream of Bunny Girl Senpai</item>
    <item>Radiant</item>
    <item>Tom Clancy\'s Jack Ryan</item>
    <item>Titans</item>
    <item>Val x Love</item>
  </string-array>
  <string-array name="tv_show_synopsis">
    <item>A story full of laughs follows sanda fighter Gu Xiao Man and school genius Zuo An as they chase after love.</item>
    <item>The passionate story of an elementary school student whose thoughts and dreams revolve almost entirely around the love of soccer. 11-year-old Tsubasa Oozora started playing football at a very young age, and while it was mostly just a recreational sport for his friends, for him, it developed into something of an obsession.</item>
    <item>A bullied teenager turns to beauty pageants as a way to exact her revenge, with the help of a disgraced coach who soon realizes he\'s in over his head.</item>
    <item>Set two generations before the destruction of the legendary Man of Steels home planet, Krypton follows Supermans grandfather — whose House of El was ostracized and shamed - as he fights to redeem his familys honor and save his beloved world from chaos.</item>
    <item>In a place where young witches, vampires, and werewolves are nurtured to be their best selves in spite of their worst impulses, Klaus Mikaelsons daughter, 17-year-old Hope Mikaelson, Alaric Saltzmans twins, Lizzie and Josie Saltzman, among others, come of age into heroes and villains at The Salvatore School for the Young and Gifted.</item>
    <item>Seth is a boy who seeks to become a great magician, and a group of witches who seek to travel to the Radiant. Radiant is a mythical land that spawns monsters called Néméses which fall to the world from the sky. While traveling, they are also hunted by The Inquisition.</item>
    <item>Puberty Syndrome—a rumored, mysterious syndrome that only affects those in their puberty. For example, a bunny girl suddenly appeared in front of Sakuta Azusagawa. The bunny girls real identity is Mai Sakurajima, a teenage celebrity who is currently an inactive high school senior. For some reason, her charming figure does not reflect in the eyes of others. In the course of revealing the mystery behind this phenomenon, Sakuta begins to explore his feelings towards Mai. Set in a city where the skies and seas shine, Sakuta unfolds the meaning behind his bizarre encounters on women with the said syndrome.</item>
    <item>When CIA analyst Jack Ryan stumbles upon a suspicious series of bank transfers his search for answers pulls him from the safety of his desk job and catapults him into a deadly game of cat and mouse throughout Europe and the Middle East, with a rising terrorist figurehead preparing for a massive attack against the US and her allies.</item>
    <item>A team of young superheroes led by Nightwing (formerly Batman\'s first Robin) form to combat evil and other perils.</item>
    <item>High schooler Akutsu Takuma has learned to accept his lonely lot in life and is content surrounded by his studies, but when the god Odin taps him to save the world alongside nine Valkyries fueled by intimacy, Takuma can say good-bye to his solitary existence.</item>
  </string-array>
  <array name="tv_show_photo">
    <item>@drawable/poster_all</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_captain</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_insatiable</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_krypton</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_legacies</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_rascal</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_radiant</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_tom</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_titans</item>
    <item>@drawable/poster_val</item>
  </array>

  <string name="change_language_settings">Change Language Settings</string>ff
</resources>
